[Applause]
[Music]
yeah the Rena was easy and our loan from
manual Life Financial really helped out
well a basement Suite that's pretty
handy the financing was
simple well you shouldn't have any
trouble renting this place out except
we're not renting it
why here
Dad you want me to live in a basement
like a rat throw Bry in a cubby hole
like a circus freak we just th oh I get
it now this was your idea oh here we go
yeah can't send me out on an ice flow so
throw them in a basement like an old
potato and a root cell we thought you'd
be happy I am happy you knucklehead I
got a nice apartment in an upscale
retirement community why would I want to
live in this mold trap listening to you
two CP about the kids at your morgage
all the time I want to go home it's taco
night and Jaws is on the big
screen manual Life Financial might want
to ask before you just go ahead and
build an in losw sweet just say it I
fought on the Arden and it was Cozier I
wouldn't keep a dog down here a dog
[Applause]